Finally.
21 & Over is a comedy film directed by Jon Lucas.
Brilliant student Jeff Chang has the most
important interview of his life tomorrow.
But today is still his birthday, what starts off as a casual celebration with friends
evolves into a night of debauchery that risks to derail his life plan.
Miller, played by Miles Teller.
Casey, played by Skylar Astin.
Jeff Chang, played by Justin Chon.
Nicole, played by Sarah Wright.
Dr. Chang, played by François Chau.
Randy, played by Jonathan Keltz.
21 & Over is a 2013 American comedy film written and directed by Jon
Lucas and Scott Moore, in their directorial debut.
The film stars Justin Chon, Miles Teller, and Skylar Astin, and follows a trio of friends who go out drinking to
celebrate one of their 21st birthdays despite having a medical school interview the following morning.
The film was released on March 1, 2013, and received generally
negative reviews from critics with a gross of $48 million.
The film explores themes of alcohol, birthday, friends, debauchery.
The tone is lighthearted.